Adnan Hassan

Frontend React Js Developer

Personal details

Adnan Hassan



ah5404219@gmail.com



+923476275532



Johar Town Shan bhatti road Lahore



github. com/adnanhassan1234



linkedin.com/in/adnanhassan-5429301b7

Skills

React Js

JavaScript

HTML5

Material UI

React-Bootstrap

Bootstrap5

CSS3

SCSS

Tailwind CSS

API integrations

Github

Profile

My name is Adnan Hassan and I am a graduate in computer science. I have 1 year and 3 months of professional experience building frontend applications or clientside web applications using React js, I use the latest technology to build web pages and integrate APIs.

Education

BS Computer Science

University of Lahore

2018 - 2022

Experience

React Js Dveloper

Mar 2022 - Mar 2023

Software Alliance, Lahore

I year of hands-on experience in professional software development or building frontend application or client side web application by using hooks and work with API integrations in react js.

Frontend Developer

Aug 2020 - Jan 2021

Softelio, Lahore

I have 6 month experience in frontend web designing with html css bootstrap and javaScript. I worked for 6 month in Softelio company Lahore and i have worked on multiple projects.

Proects

goWild website:

URL: https://gowild.appscorridor.com/

This project is Admin Dashboard, where Admins can manage routes and users with API integration by using axios and Yup Formik validation. Technologies used: React Js, JavaScript, React-Bootstrap, HTML, SCSS

PrizeManner website:

URL: https://web.prizeminer.appscorridor.com/

This dashboard is a winner-prize-based web applications and integration API's with user role crud system by using axios library. Technologies used: React Js, JavaScript, React-Bootstrap, HTML, SCSS

PieceMaker webite:

URL: <u>https://piecemaker.netlify.app/</u>

This dashboard is provide a comprehensive management system for various user roles and functionalities. The project includes several pages such as User, End User, Sub Admin, Challenges, and Sponsorship. Technologies used: React Js, JavaScript, React-Bootstrap, HTML, SCSS

Wallet website:

URL: https://violett-spadsoft.netlify.app/

The wallet dashboard is designed for manage a data by using barchart, Line-chart with slider wallet card and also designed chat system. Technologies used: React Js, JavaScript , React-Bootstrap, HTML, SCSS

Interest

- Programming
- Article reading
- Book reading
- Travelling